Thank you.
Hey, how's it going?
Come here for a second, please.
Hello.
Have a seat.
Come here and have a seat.
Cross your legs.
Have a seat.
Come here.
I'm talking to you guys.
Have a seat.
Please have a seat.
You too.
Have a seat.
All the way down.
How about you join?
How about you join me over here?
Since we want to play fuck-fuck games.
Have...
IDs.
Please get them now.
I have them in my phone.
It's in my bag over there.
It's in your where?
It's in a bag over there.
Okay, I'll get it.
IDs.
I don't have mine.
We're going to fucking...
Stop playing this game.
Take your head off.
What are you doing?
Don't look at her.
Look at me.
What are you doing?
You want to go to Santa Rita?
That's fine by me.
Santa Rita?
Let's go.
ID.
Where is it?
Stand up.
Turn around.
No, no, no.
Why in your stance?
Take her over there.
Sit her down.
Sit up.
Why in your stance?
Don't pull away.
Stop moving.
Do you want to play adult games?
This is the adult.
Don't start crying.
We asked you for your name.
No!
Stop pulling away.
You're hurting me.
You're not being very cooperative.
I do not.
Do you have an ID in your pocket?
I do not have an ID on mine.
What's in your pockets?
So far I've got a pair of...
Do you know why we're locked here?
I'm going to hold onto these.
You justAAAA
Thank you.
You just cáck me out, OK?
By the way,
Have a seat.
ID yourself to this officer or you're going to go to jail.
I photographed this.
I tried to pull it down, but it's all wrapped up up there and there's a chain attached to it.
Yeah.
You're not under arrest.
Yeah, you're not under arrest.
You're being detained.
Why am I being detained?
Because of vandalism.
This is not vandalism.
Stand up.
She didn't want to be here.
Sorry, I just had one idea.
Who?
That's fine.
Santa Rita.
Have you ever been to Santa Rita?
No, she has ideas.
Oh, I thought you said you didn't.
Turn around.
Hands behind your back.
Plastic gloves?
I'm sorry?
Why in your stance?
Do you have any ID with you?
No.
What's this?
That feels like an ID to me.
Huh?
Is there a name on it?
So you lied to me.
You have an ID with you.
I forgot that it has my name on it.
Have a seat.
Okay, get your legs across your feet.
I'm not in the fucking mood to play games, especially with this bullshit,
but especially with the vet tomorrow, because I know exactly what this is for.
Good, good, confirmed IDs on everybody.
Yeah.
Do you have your heart ID with you?
No, I don't.
Yeah, the driver's license?
This is the state, get it.
Any, like, ID card?
I only have my school ID.
That's fine.
It has a picture of it, right?
Yes, but I have it.
Okay.
Thank you.
Whose stuff?
So I'm keeping this, just so you guys know.
This is mine now.
This is evidence of vandalism.
Tina, go ahead and sign a case of this, and we'll give you more and further.
I got pictures of all this other stuff already.
Would you take a picture of this?
Because they were going to hang this.
Yeah.
I got a couple pictures of it.
I got pictures of all that stuff.
I put this stuff on my lap.
Oh, were they posting those, pasting those up?
That's my, that's all correct.
Hey, hey, um.
Give me one second.
Okay.
Fucking felony, felony vandalism.
Hey, 1015 times 4.
This stuff right here?
Yeah.
It's fresh?
Yeah, I don't know about that.
You want me to go check the other one?
Uh, they're down.
Huh?
Yeah, go ahead.
I think they're down.
You think they're, sorry.
Yeah, I think they're down.
Oh, the cameras?
Yeah.
I think.
Try.
Go try.
If you want me to.
Yeah, go do it.
Okay.
Yeah.
And then I can, I'll try to do it real quick.
Yeah, here.
It'll last like 30 minutes, and then I can bring a car around.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because that's where, that's where the answer is.
Put your hands, put your hands behind your back.
I'm not being a vandal.
Yes, you are.
Cuts.
I'm going to confirm some things, and then we'll let you know what's going on.
Hey, Jet.
Stop what you're doing.
Go ahead and put her in handcuffs, please.
Stop.
You're being detained.
You're not arrested yet.
We'll let you know when you are.
Stand up.
I need a, I need a pair of cuffs.
Put your hands behind your back.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'm going to take this crap off first.
Something tells me that that is evidence.
Go ahead.
Why are your hands so sweaty?
Nervous about something?
No.
Okay.
Have a seat.
Hold on, hold on.
I'm having a seat.
Have a seat.
I got you.
Keep your legs out.
We're not going to play this game.
Cross them.
Since we want to be adults, we're going to have adult consequences.
You guys are going to love this area.
You can't just get up like that, okay?
You can't.
What did that mean?
It meant that you kind of lose track of what's going on.
You can't.
You can't lose track of what's going on.
are evidence yeah
there's there's a first thing of there's a first thing of adhesive right here
yeah so yeah so the cost to clean this up is more than $400 I'm not playing
games tonight send it
yeah copy
sample
this batch yeah would you go ahead and
this batch yeah would you go ahead and give C to your call let me know that
give C to your call let me know that
give C to your call let me know that we're likely 10 15 times four for
we're likely 10 15 times four for
we're likely 10 15 times four for binal is related to Marston
Yeah, I copy that.
All of the centers of the agency, that's where it's going to be.
What number?
45.
Go ahead.
What is that?
Did you have a person that you wanted to contact?
They'll ask you.
Can I come back to that one?
Yeah, they'll ask you.
If you want to give it to me, what's your phone number?
Okay.
What do you need, Mike?
You have your ID card?
Do you have it?
Okay.
.
2-9-go.
Copy.
This belongs, I don't know if you're talking to her, this belongs to her.
3-5-8, a couple, but not, I'm not sure, yep.
Hey, sorry to bug you.
He spotted a few subjects trying to throw something or mount something over Sather Gate,
and he called me and called it in, and so we responded out and detained four.
They were also, I believe they were also pasting,
and you're using buckets of paste of some sort to paste up flyers
of people who were in the area.
Charlie Kirk, Turning Point USA founder, said black women basically rally outside
Zellerbach Hall this Monday at 4.30 p.m. to protest turning points.
So they're pasted on the marble towers or marble posts of Sather Gate.
2-4-6-8-10-12-14-16-18-20,
at least maybe two dozen, if not more.
They were also trying to hoist up this paper machine,
the Shade Bug thing, over Sather Gate.
So the pasting, the pasting alone,
I'm going to hook all four of them for phoning that over,
because cleaning this stuff off is going to be problematic.
So I think at least, give me one second.
Hey, who's, can you see who's affiliated for me?
I think all four of them are affiliated.
At least one of them.
Just one of the four?
Yeah, just one of the four.
Yeah, I believe so.
Probably loosely affiliated.
One of them was wearing a keffiyeh.
The rest of them were,
you know,
either wearing hoods and COVID masks.
One of them was wearing a keffiyeh.
So they were all attempting to hide themselves.
One was wearing plastic gloves on their hands.
So.
Yeah, yep.
Yeah, this is going to actually soak up my whole patrol team,
because we're going to go down to the women's basketball game
to help us out.
We're going to go down to, if we're lucky,
three and one, if not two and one.
So we'll do our best.
But I'm not going to, I'm not fucking around.
But we're going to take these folks to the jail.
So.
I think that's what we're going to do.
Okay.
Cool.
Thank you.
Bye.
What do you want to take with you?
We haven't taken my personal items with you.
That's it.
Like a phone, an ID.
I need you to get your car.
Okay.
This stuff is going to be here.
So the stuff that I don't,
the stuff that's not a personal item,
if you want to have it in the department?
Okay.
So you're going to get a sheet with all your stuff.
It will come out on this side.
835.
Okay.
We're going to go to Santa Rita.
Oh, yeah.
So I'm going to send two cars with probably three officers.
Okay.
And if we need fit force, we'll divide and conquer.
We'll send another unit out in just a second.
I'm going to tell all four of them that they're under arrest for the vandalism
related to the poster.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure they all know they're going to do it.
I want to split.
I did not get pictures of these ones on the back at all.
I know Frank was taking some pictures too.
We can come back and hash out what pictures we have.
We don't have.
I also took a, I don't know what you got from 98.
I took a brief statement from him over the phone.
Yeah.
Just to see if he saw any of the postering stuff.
I found a good camera.
And then I think there was just, I don't know if there was too much going on.
Or what with the computer.
But the computer was like, oh, I got to reset.
Oh, just close out all those windows.
I think is what it was.
I meant to help the EP officer, but we got to take.
He left a note.
Yeah.
I'll get him the video.
We're going to, I don't want to send, I can't send four cops, but I'll send three.
Yeah.
Because how long is Abby going to be here for?
Until midnight.
I'll try to get her to stay till one.
Yeah.
12 to nine.
But that's fine.
Um, it's Sunday night.
Huh?
No, I padded, I padded most of them or all of them.
So I got the scissors and the gloves and stuff.
Um, we're going to go to Rita with all four of them.
Yep.
Okay.
Um, wait for, what I want to do is split one and one field, field and operandize.
See if they're willing to give a statement so we can check that box.
Um, I'm going to tell them right now what they're under arrest for.
Okay.
Um, but let's split them up.
Let's get them separated, brandize them individually, and then she can get
savings from them if they're willing to.
They're not going to, but we're going to try.
And then do you want to get, uh, pictures so whoever's here can start
hashed out CARs?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's take pictures of them.
No, we need individual pictures of them?
Yes.
Yeah, let's do that.
Okay.
Let's start with that.
Um, no, no, still, I don't have my work phone with me.
I actually do have my work phone.
No, mine's actually closed.
Oh, I don't.
You have your work phone?
Yeah, I have it.
Cool.
Let's start with that.
Okay.
Uh, let's start.
Who's getting the other vehicle?
Uh, handshake right now.
Okay, cool.
Okay.
All right, listen up.
I'm Sergeant Tinney.
I am placing all four of you in arrest for felony vandalism.
You will be transported to Santa Rita Jail in Dublin.
If anyone has any medical conditions, let it known, let us know now.
It'll make the booking process a lot longer, and you will delay the process,
which is a nonviolent crime, but it is felony vandalism.
If you want to draw it out, that's fine.
You don't have to pay me.
We get paid by the hour.
But you're going to the Santa Rita Jail in Dublin.
Do you guys know what that means?
You guys are all under arrest for felony vandalism.
Anyone have any questions?
I have a question.
Yes, please.
Uh, I have a medication that I take weekly.
Yep.
Is that something that's just not...
You're not going to be in jail for that long.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thank you for your time.
Later tonight, tomorrow.
Okay.
That's my guess.
It's just my guess.
That's it.
This is a nonviolent crime.
This is...
I'm saying vandalism, and I'm saying felony vandalism.
I have a question.
Yes.
Will our property be returned to us when we leave the jail?
If it...
Unless it's evidence, yes, it will be.
So, like, my Clipper card?
Oh, we'll give that back to you beforehand.
We'll give that to you back for...
I do need that to get home.
Yeah.
No, you'll get that.
Um, if I'm seizing it, you won't get it back.
But bags like that, you...
We'll just keep it until you come get it.
Okay.
We'll make sure you get a receipt.
Any other questions about procedure?
Just about procedure?
Yeah.
I have a worried look on your face.
Do you have a question?
I'm just really scared.
Yeah, you should be.
I've been to Santa Rita jail.
It's not a fucking nice place.
But we all make adult decisions.
Everyone here is an adult, right?
I have a question.
Yes, please.
This thing I was...
Can I have that as well?
No.
I'm going to keep that.
Yeah, they won't allow that in the jail.
The scarf, no.
It'll go with the rest of your stuff.
Oh, my God.
I paid money for that.
You probably...
If you're going to think about this thing...
Yeah.
You're doing stuff like this.
I was, like, waiting for this.
I'm wearing it.
What do you mean?
You're, like, not giving me that.
The jail is not going to let you wear anything more than, like, a shirt and maybe a sweatshirt.
No face covering.
Yeah.
Not only that, so when a crime is committed and you're concealing your identity, that's
an additional crime on you.
These are things that people don't think about.
Like, it's a harmless thing.
Why would you fix it?
I've got pictures of all four.
Perfect.
Let's just peel off the man.
We've got a...
You were F-ing her.
Confirmed ID?
No.
Yes.
Yeah, I think they gave you that.
He came back out of Illinois.
Yeah.
Montana?
He came back out of Montana.
Okay.
Over here.
Do you want me to start...
I'm going to start taking one.
Yeah.
Take one.
So you're going to drive, too, since you have a vehicle.
Yep.
Peel one off.
Field Miranda.
Okay.
Get a good waiver, a good invocation.
If there's some stuff you don't understand, clarify.
Document that on your body cam.
See if she'll give a statement.
Yeah.
3-5.
You can put in 2-5.
That's mine.
Okay.
What's the amount of time we can pass before we get to the next question?
What's the amount of time we can pass before we can get this expunged?
If the, whatever crime, misdemeanor or felony is not charged by the DA's office, you could
petition or perhaps there's a mechanism in place.
That automatically requires our department to send you and the DA's office a letter saying
this is a detention only because the DA's office didn't charge it.
This is a detention only and then it doesn't really hang on your record at all.
Now we have a local record of it, but in California, if you apply for a job, I think there's some
legislation requiring or around what employers can ask of a person.
Does that make sense?
Yes.
So if you don't get charged.
This becomes a detention and detention only, not an arrest in the state of California per
legislation.
If you get arrested, what will be the option to get exiled?
It depends on if it gets charged or not.
So the next step is our report goes to the DA's office.
DA's office may look at it and go, no, this is not worth our time.
It's a detention only.
If they go, oh, we're going to charge this, then you have to go through a little bit more
process with the court to figure out.
What they're going to require you to do, if anything, maybe it goes through a couple
hearings and they decide to just toss it away.
If it goes all the way to conviction or a plea, like you plea no contest to it, you
have other options, but they're limited because of the kind of guilty plea or the conviction,
the found guilty part of it.
That's way further down the line.
This is not a violent crime.
This is a property issue.
And in the grand scheme of things in this county.
Uh, pretty low on the, on the priority, does that make sense?
So this case has to get charged before you have to consider anything more serious than,
than, uh, learning kind of a hard lesson and perhaps having the inconvenience of whatever
this leads to, if that makes sense for the next 24 hours or whatever it is.
Mm.
Yeah, that's, I'm not taking that as evidence.
We'll get a paper bag to separate that stuff.
So this, no, no, I'm taking that as evidence.
Yes.
That's, that's part of the vandalism for me.
So this right here, this is not, this is all going to go back together because that was
yours too.
Right?
Uh, the staplers here somewhere.
Did it fall down?
I don't know.
Okay.
I don't know if they fixed it.
I'm not the...
Hi, how's it going?
Oh, no.
I just see that.
This way, not this way.
Just over yonder would be great?
I want to go home.
Then you can go that way.
Oh yeah.
Okay, just can we keep this area clear?
Okay.
Is that okay with you?
How about walk with me?
Okay.
Over here?
Is that where you want to go?
Yes.
Okay, yeah, you're good.
Thanks, man.
What did I miss?
They said they only have three names.
Two-nine, give me the last names of who you ran out.
Two-nine.
Hey.
Hey, 77.
That's, yeah, that one.
Yeah, do we have an FI on her?
And she said any.
negative
We can go and send one car, okay, I'm gonna well
Yeah, we're just we're just gonna send I'm they're all adults right I'm comfortable sending them just to in to break on
You have
I
Know
No, let's do that yeah
you
Have any injuries like that
Middle of marina
Thank you.
I'll send you a number.
That's true.
That's a sweet spot.
Hi.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
I'm with the Daily California.
Yep.
Can you guys share anything about what's going on right here?
No comment.
Not at this time.
Nope.
Okay.
Thanks.
Searched?
Okay.
Negative all around?
Yeah, negative.
Okay.
But this is safekeeping?
That is safekeeping.
Okay.
Property right here?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It's Joe.
Hi.
How can I help you?
I'm just watching.
I'm not interfering.
Could you watch from over there, please?
Where?
About the brick area over there.
I feel...
Well, I'm...
Isn't the lot six feet away?
If I'm six feet away...
No.
There's no distance requirement, minimum or maximum.
I'm suggesting over there.
I really don't want to make this into an adversarial thing.
Okay.
I am requesting that you go over there.
Thank you.
Okay, okay.
Is it that little thing there?
Yeah, it's gonna be...
Oh.
Okay.
Hey, 9-7, are we making sure that we're checking for fit and placement?
Just make sure fit and placement are, fit and placement and double lock are there.
Who's driving that one?
3-5, 3-5 is probably going to have to pick it up.
Yeah, wait for him to come over.
Any folks who want me to call or message?
Uh, no? Okay.
Thanks for asking.
Thanks.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I'm going to send all of my folks, you're going to stay here and hopefully chill with me.
It's already past 12. Are you good to stay until like 0-1?
Yeah.
Okay.
So, you're going to jump in with 8-0?
Yeah, we'll go with 8-0.
That sounds good.
Okay.
Um...
That car's good to go. That car has two.
And we'll head up?
Yeah.
Okay.
Yep.
Um, I'm going to keep 7-7 here.
I'm going to send you solo to meet up with them.
Yep.
Cool.
Uh, sorry.
The, uh, the, the, the gentleman over there, he has asking names and everything.
Can you just stand by?
Oh, I told him no comment. He's from Daily Cal.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, let's just peel off another one and get that going.
Please stand up.
Are you picking me up?
Uh, please stand up.
Yeah.
Is there anything else?
There's an old property that can't go with you.
So, this is, this is not, I'm not seizing this.
This is going to get back to you.
But, um, we'll say to Rita, accept clothing.
Like this.
This is going to go with you.
You can't take it.
You can't wear it.
And that suit, they don't want you to, they don't want to hurt yourself.
Yes, this makes sense.
So, I'm going to send you this.
Worst case scenario, it comes back and you have to make it up from us.
Okay.
I'm not seizing this.
This gets back to you.
Okay.
Is that cool?
Yeah.
Is there anything in your pockets that is, like, weapons or...
Drugs or anything that the jail won't accept?
I have keys on my waist.
Keys?
No, they'll take keys.
They're on my waist.
Yeah, they'll take keys.
They'll take keys.
Well, you need the house keys, right?
They are my house keys.
And did we give your clipper card back to you?
I don't have mine.
They have it.
All right.
Go with this, uh, Officer Matthews.
Give me one second.
You get a, can you walk her over to the car?
Yep.
Yeah.
I'm going to give this to you.
That's what I'm going to go with.
Uh...
I got a picture of the ID.
Yep.
I'll take that.
Thank you.
And then, you said...
This was your bag, correct?
Okay.
And that's all...
Whose is this?
Is this phone?
Is it yours?
That phone and the keys.
But this is going to go with you?
Okay.
The cone's not yours.
All right.
I'm going to...
You'll know each other, right?
So, if I put her stapler in, or her staples in her scissors, will it get back to her or should I keep it separate?
It'll get back to her.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you.
I'm going to have you stand up and we're going to walk over here now, okay?
And that's going to go with, you want, you need this, right?
Yes.
Do you have anything sharp on you?
Anything that's going to hurt me?
And then we tell this to everybody at this time.
Anything on you, like,
anything that's going to hurt you?
Anything?
S-290 request.
And what does it say?
Just on the...
I'm not sure if there's an on-call station engineer
or someone in facility service or the latter,
but we'll need it to try to remove this string from the...
Do you have a layer under this?
Okay, nothing in pockets?
Yeah.
Gotcha.
And then I'm going to take your record.
Okay.
I honestly don't remember.
It might be...
Shh.
Sorry.
Did you do that, sir?
Did you do that?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, perfect.
That's how I do it, yeah.
Do you want to tell me where you're going to go?
Yep.
Say bye.
Sorry.
Yep.
Uh, I got a post-Moranian statement from her saying that they panned all this stuff on
the walls.
They were hanging the mosquito.
It's an art piece.
Did you symbolize anything?
She just said it's an art piece.
Okay.
And who, uh, did she implement it?
Indicate?
Indicate.
Who made it?
No, no, no.
Oh.
That all four of them were involved in painting the, in attaching the fires?
Uh, I, she said we were.
Cool.
Um, and then she said one of them made that.
Okay.
She did not, but one of them did.
Yep.
Cool.
This one?
Okay.
Ready?
Uh, I have a question.
No.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
I'll just ask you one question.
You're right.
Two-night.
.
Copy.
that is none of your business if they wanted to tell you they could tell you
that because they already knew that but I'm not sharing that information with
you
oh yeah yeah
good to go!
what are you taking Come on pull over here
This is a personal property
that will be returned this actually it's
Can I just text my work phone?
yeah do you want me to work on it
I'll get you a barber receipt
yeah
yeah just text me what I just shit
we'll come yeah yep
acquainted without far這
Yep. Yeah roger that. Alright, so let's figure this out here. So actually, would you would
you mind just ferrying stuff? I'll just stand by and guard. If you wouldn't mind ferrying
stuff and we'll stage it in evidence. Just start with that. And maybe this. So stand
by. I have no idea dude I don't want to know. So. Yeah they do. Yeah there's two of us.
Yeah so we're just gonna put these, actually that's just gonna live in there. That's
sealed. Yeah. And that's sealed. So I'll, we'll start with this. And I'm not going
going to put on top of the hard stuff and that's covered. Would you just
transport that into evidence? Just be worried because I think I got it on
myself here. Um, and I'll stand by for this and then we're going to go.
Excuse me. Uh, no comment. I know you said, but can you provide the name for
our arresting officer? We haven't figured that out yet. Who just arrested
them? Well, I placed him under arrest. My name is Sergeant Tinney. Yeah,
that's T. I. N. N. E. Y. Gotcha. Um, batch number 29 to 929. Gotcha. And
you're with U. C. P. D. U. C. P. D.
Yeah, I think that'll do for now.
And no comment.
Do you have anything to offer about anything here? I do not. Uh, by policy, I
am not, uh,
being cleared to give official comments on a
active investigation or a criminal caper. Uh, the P. I. O. Would be the one
that does that. Unless he gives me special dispensation to do that. I
didn't copy that last.
Yeah, I copy standing by.
I kind of like like look at it. Just not touch it. You look at it. Hey, guys, you can
look at, just don't get much closer. What's it made out of cardboard it looks like?
Do you mind if I take some photos from the newspaper? Yeah, go ahead man.
Thank you.
Or was it a mosquito?
That's exactly what it is. Yeah.
Mosquito.
Was it being hung up when you found it?
No comment.
I just came out alive right now.
Who's the PIO on duty tonight?
There is no PIO on duty.
Not tonight?
Even with the Charlie Kirk stuff?
How big of a department do you think we are?
We have a 24-hour PIO?
That's their stuff.
Someone on staff.
I am the highest ranking person right now.
Why?
With a lot of work.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, I get paid a lot of money.
That's good.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I think someone else could probably tell you that.
You guys are...
That's Daily Cal?
Yeah.
Also with...
Oh.
Are you with Daily Cal too?
Oh, then why don't you talk to each other?
What do you want to have?
A second.
So, can you draw down the clearing of these people?
Okay.
Where's Aberdeen?
Over there.
And I'm just trying to figure out what they're talking about.
I don't know.
I'm trying to figure out in the back.
What's this?
I'm sorry?
Sculpture.
All of the above.
What time are you back?
Monday?
Or today?
5 p.m.
All right.
Then I'm going to get you.
You can do your sup tomorrow.
If you think you need a sup.
Do you think you can carry that thing?
Probably.
It's just hard work.
Yeah, it's kind of fragile.
Maybe around the tail.
Oh, yeah, that works.
All right, you got it all?
All right.
I'll be there.
I'm waiting for facilities.
Is there any more?
There's a good spot.
You got it?
Nope.
Let's see what I got.
I got pictures of that.
Yeah, I got a lot more.
One over.
This is where you're hungry.
Could it be?
Like, could it be the...
That's so fucking...
No, it could be a cockroach.
I guess.
I just...
I think they're just crawling.
They're cockroaches, too.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, they're with their blood suckers.
It's like...
It's like a blank pad suit on your ears.
Yeah.
I mean, it's all good.
It's all good.
All these are purchasing books.
Yeah.
Oh, that was cool.
No comment.
No.
Okay.
I have a totally separate, unrelated question, is it illegal to ask a cop for a ride in their
car?
It's not legal at all.
It's not legal at all?
No.
I mean, most are going to probably frown at you and go, what are you talking about?
But it's context specific.
If it's just random, it's going to be strange.
If it's going to be connected to some sort of other business-related contact, it's not
odd at all.
If you happen to fall off your scooter or something or bike on campus, you don't need
...
So it's out of curiosity what it looks like?
Yeah.
We give people courtesy rides all the time, but largely it's related to some other contact.
So injury, some sort of crime report, if they're a victim of something, if they're a witness
in something.
It just depends on context.
But it's not unlawful at all.
I saw a video ...
Do you know?
Yeah.
We taught a lot ofThank you.
Thank you for having me.
Bye, bye Are you in there?
Yeah, I see you there.
Thanks.